

LE THANH HANG

Date of birth: Sep 30, 1994

Gender: Female

Phone: 01689688852

Email: lethanhhang309@gmail.com

Address: 223 Hoang Hoa Tham, Phu Nhuan District,

HCMC

Website: https://www.facebook.com/hang309

CAREER AIMS

Gain knowledges, experiences in pharmacy field and improve necessary skills as well. Hope to be a member of a company which has professional, friendly working environment; work for a long-term and devote all of abilities to the company.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2017 Ho Chi Minh City Medicine and Pharmacy University

Faculty of Pharmacy

EXPERIENCE

06/2018- Now Medical Representative ETC at Vitabiotics

Representative Office

01/2018-06/2018 Medical Representative ETC at Pharmevo

(pvt.)Ltd.

Base Town: HCM City Children's Hospital

10/2017 – 01/2018 Purchasing Trainee at Sanofi Aventis

JOB DESCRIPTION (Med Rep)

- -Building the relation with physician, pharmacist, especially Head or Vice Head of Departments in hospitals.
- -Analyzing strong point of product and introduce to physician.
- -Understanding and capture the activities of distributors including programs on product detailing, take care of hospital departments, activities of distributor's employees.
- -Understanding and update the status of directly competitive drugs (same active ingredient) and in the same treatment group.

SKILLS

Computer MS Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Outlook.

Time management Arrange schedule to work effectively with the highest

productivity.

Team working Well cooperate with colleagues and independently work as well.